How I feel about certain design choices with little to no explanation.
Yes.
Absolutely not.
For me, this one's 50-50.
100% no.
Yes, and I don't care that it's impractical.
I hate these.
I think I might hate this even more.
Yes, of course.
No.
Yes, I've grown really fond of this.
Surprisingly, I actually like this.
Okay, so here we have Laverne Cox.
I'm going to tell you now.
I'm not going to give you designer names, etc, etc.
I'm going to just give you my opinions.
And up top, what I'm seeing here is Egyptians on a black lip.
Denim on denim on denim.
Black birds singing in the dead of night.
It's really bridesmaid-y, right?
If by chance you're curious about why I feel this way about these looks,
come on over to the Amandaverse.
I know, I know.
Over here, I talk about racism.
I talk about police brutality, social injustice, all the things.
But if you want to see another side of SEALs,
head on over to my Patreon, the Amandaverse,
and join up with the rest of the SEALs squad.